<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!-- Ammunition descriptions, taken from Veer's Simple Ammo Stats. -->

<string_table>

	<string id="ammo_12.7x55_ap_descr">
		<text>The armour-piercing 12.7x55mm subsonic cartridge is used in the VKS bullpup sniper rifle. The cartridge can carry a projectile weighing between from 59 grams (911 grains) and 76 g (1173 grains), yielding massive amounts of kinetic energy.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-fmj_descr">
		<text>The .45 calibre full metal jacket round has enjoyed popularity for a hundred years thanks to its ballistic performance and a relatively small propelling charge. As a result, the bullet in this round is relatively slow but highly accurate and provides considerable stopping power, with high damage fall-off.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-hydro_descr">
		<text>This unusual .45 ACP calibre round consists of a jacketed soft point bullet with a hollow steel core, possessing both their advantages and disadvantages.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-12.7x55-fmj_descr">
		<text>The full metal jacket 12.7x55mm subsonic cartridge is used in the VKS bullpup sniper rifle. The cartridge can carry a projectile weighing between from 59 grams (911 grains) and 76 g (1173 grains), yielding massive amounts of kinetic energy.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-12x70-buck_descr">
		<text>Standard 12 gauge shell filled with 8 mm shot. Highly lethal at close range. Only suitable for use with smoothbore weapons.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] multiple pellets, shorter eff. range</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-12x76-dart_descr">
		<text>12 gauge dart round, normally used for hunting big game but also suitable for other purposes, including puncturing armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-12x76-bull_descr">
		<text>12 gauge custom-made slugs for putting down dinosaurs and mutants. Slug inside is made of lead covered in copper that has steel, dart-like insert inside. Slug is very long and has got big powder load. It really can break your hands with recoil.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ammo-12x76-zhekan_descr">
		<text>This heavy 12 gauge slug round is normally used for hunting big game, but is also good for other purposes. Instead of piercing, this hefty slug simply crushes through armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-338-lapua_descr">
		<text>The .338 Lapua Magnum is a specialised rimless bottlenecked centrefire cartridge developed for military long-range sniper rifles. The Afghanistan War and Iraq War made it a combat-proven round with ready and substantial ammunition availability. The .338 Lapua is a dual-purpose anti-personnel and anti-materiel round, but its anti-materiel potential is limited.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-357-hp_descr">
		<text>The .357 HP round is a hollow-point bullet. The purpose of the round is to slow down upon impact, which decreases its penetration, but at the same time causes larger internal tissue damage. \n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-ap_descr">
		<text>Military 5.45x39 calibre 7N22 armour-piercing round for automatic rifles of Warsaw Pact countries. The bullet contains a hard-alloy armour-piercing penetrator. Effective against body armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-ep_descr">
		<text>Military 5.45x39 calibre HP is an hollow point round for automatic rifles of Warsaw Pact countries.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-fmj_descr">
		<text>Military 5.45x39 calibre 7N6 was the first standard issue round for automatic rifles of Warsaw Pact countries using the new intermediate cartridge. Provides better accuracy than the 7.62 calibre round thanks to reduced recoil and a 100-metre increase in range.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ap_descr">
		<text>The latest NATO military 5.56x45 calibre enhanced penetration round, known as M855A1, used by the US armed forces. Increased effectiveness against both body armour and soft tissue.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1] armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ss190_descr">
		<text>A standard-issue NATO 5.56x45 calibre round with an hollow point tip.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-fmj_descr">
		<text>A standard-issue NATO 5.56x45 calibre M193 round specially designed for accurate automatic fire. Provides good ballistic characteristics, having been designed on the basis of a hunting round. Well known for being used in the Vietnam war and having great performance against tissue, but limited penetration.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss190_descr">
		<text>The FN 5.7x28mm is a high velocity cartridge designed and manufactured by FN Herstal. It is a bottlenecked centrefire cartridge that is somewhat similar to the .22 Hornet or .22 K-Hornet. The 5.7x28mm was developed in conjunction with the FN P90 personal defense weapon (PDW) and FN Five-seven pistol, in response to NATO requests for a replacement for the 9x19mm Parabellum cartridge.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-4.6x30-fmj_descr">
		<text>The HK 4.6x30mm cartridge is a type of ammunition primarily used in the Heckler &amp; Koch MP7 personal defense weapon (PDW). It is designed to minimize weight and recoil while increasing penetration of body armor. It features a bottlenecked case and a pointed, steel-core, brass-jacketed bullet.
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss195_descr">
		<text>The SS195 FN 5.7x28mm is an expansive cartridge designed and manufactured by FN Herstal. It is a bottlenecked centrefire cartridge that is somewhat similar to the .22 Hornet or .22 K-Hornet. \n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-50-bmg_descr">
		<text>The .50 Browning Machine Gun (12.7x99mm NATO and designated as the 50 Browning by the C.I.P.) is a cartridge developed for the Browning .50 caliber machine gun in the late 1910s, entering official service in 1921. Under STANAG 4383, it is a standard cartridge for NATO forces as well as many non-NATO countries. The cartridge itself has been made in many variants: multiple generations of regular ball, tracer, armor-piercing (AP), incendiary, and saboted sub-caliber rounds. The rounds intended for machine guns are made into a continuous belt using metallic links.
		\nThe .50 BMG cartridge is also used in long-range target and anti-materiel rifles, as well as other .50-caliber machine guns.
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p_descr">
		<text>The 7.62x25mm cartridge is a Russian bottle-necked pistol cartridge widely used in former Soviet satellite states, China and Pakistan among other countries. A Lot of these rounds are still available in the Zone. This 7.62x25mm Tokarev cartridge comprises a bullet with lead round nose, polymer coated (LRNPC) bullet intended for sport shooting and hunting. By design, this cartridge provides a considerable stopping power effect as well as causing substantial adverse effects on the target after impact, this is at the cost of penetration capabilities, even against basic ballistic protection. \n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-ps_descr">
		<text>The steel core 7.62x25mm cartridge is a Russian bottle-necked pistol cartridge widely used in former Soviet satellite states, China and Pakistan among other countries. This 7.62x25mm Tokarev cartridge displays a bullet with steel core (Pst) and a steel sleeve.  It's very effective against medium armored targets and is thus appreciated in the Zone. \n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_ap_descr">
		<text>7.62x39 M43 is an armour piercing round produced in China, which is why it's often referred to as "7.62x39 CN". This round features a mild steel core which enhances its penetration capabilities. This Chinese round (as well as all other M43 ammunition) is currently banned for import in the US because US federal law classifies the round as an armour-piercing handgun round. This classification is based on materials and bullet design rather than on empirical ability to penetrate armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_fmj_descr">
		<text>7.62x39 Full Metal Jacket is one of the most commonly used types of ammunition, especially in Africa and in the Middle East. Some nicknamed it the "Round of the Revolution" due to its favored use by both terrorist and criminal organizations. Due to the sheer power of the round most military organizations have turned to using additional steel plates to counter 7.62x39 as there is a high probability of encountering it in combat situations.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_ap_descr">
		<text>Military 7.62x51 calibre M61 armor-piercing round with a hardened steel core. It retains high damage while greatly improving performance against body armor.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_fmj_descr">
		<text>The 7.62x51 NATO round is a military variant of the .308 round which was used as a standard-issue by the NATO forces until 5.56 ammunition was introduced in the '70s in the Vietnam War. At present, it is most commonly employed by private military contractors all over the world. The 7.62x51 round is a very common machine gun calibre, and can also be used in battle or sniper rifles.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x54_7n14_descr">
		<text>The 7.62x54 calibre 7N14 is an armour-piercing cartridge. The bullet has a steel core to penetrate body armour or light barriers, and a boat-tail base to increase accuracy.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-7n1_descr">
		<text>A 7.62x54 calibre sniper round with a steel penetrator specially designed for the SVD. It's steel core is made to pierce light armors. Very common in the zone, these bullets are quite cheap.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-ap_descr">
		<text>The 7.62x54mm calibre 7N13 armor-piercing machine gun round. It is a high-powered round and thanks to a hard steel core it possesses quite good penetrative capabilities.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-r_descr">
		<text>Special type of 7.62x54r rounds specifically designed for the constraints of light-machine guns like PKP or PKM, allowing easier full auto recoil control and a cheaper price per ammunition thanks to the reduced amounts of gun powder (grains). The hardened steel heads tend to better penetrate hard objects compared to other 7.62x54r rounds, but at the cost of soft targets over penetration. The reduced grains also tend to have a lower impact and thus reduced internal damages compared to standard sniper variants of 7.62x54r ammunition.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.92x33_ap_descr">
		<text>7.92x57 SA is a round that was used by the British military against armoured targets. It features a hardened steel core which gives it higher piercing capabilities. Used primarily for long range shots, the grain quality of this round is higher than the standard. This cartridge is supported by several sniper rifles.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-7.92x33_fmj_descr">
		<text>The 7.92x57 Mauser round was adopted by the German Empire and then the Third Reich. It was one of the most popular cartridges in the period of two world wars. However, nowadays, the round is primarily used for hunting and sports.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x18-ap_descr">
		<text>RG028 is a cartridge used for its armour penetration capabilities. The goal of the RG028 was to become a counter to body armour; for this reason, it's loaded with a hardened steel core. Unfortunately, the round itself isn't much of an improvement over the standard, it just has a stronger impact than typical 9x18 round.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x18-fmj_descr">
		<text>A full metal jacket round with a steel penetrator and a lead core under a metal jacket. Provides good stopping power but is ineffective against body armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x18-pmm_descr">
		<text>This round contains a bullet with enhanced stopping power thanks to its hollow point. Ineffective against body armour, but high damage against flesh.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x19-ap_descr">
		<text>This Russian 9x19 calibre bullet comes with a hard steel core and increased pressure. Designed to enhance armour penetrating capabilities of small arms and submachine guns.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x19-fmj_descr">
		<text>This basic 9x19 calibre round with a jacketed bullet has good characteristics while being simple to produce. The round is popular due to the fact that international conventions prohibit the use of expanding ammunition in combat. Ineffective against body armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x19-pbp_descr">
		<text>This 9x19 calibre jacketed hollow-point bullet with an expanding hollow has high stopping power and low ricochet propensity. Used by police and for self-defense. Ineffective against body armour due to its low penetration potential, but flesh damage. One of the cheapest ammo to efficiently kill mutants in the zone.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x39-ap_descr">
		<text>The SP-6 is a subsonic armour-piercing round with a jacketed soft point bullet with a hard steel core that protrudes from the casing. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing. Used by special services of Warsaw Pact countries. Effective against light body armour.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored enemies
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[d_red] - %c[ui_gray_2] sub-sonic ammunition\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] greatly increased projectile drop with distance</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-9x39-pab9_descr">
		<text>The SP-5 is a subsonic rifle round with a bimetallic casing. The round contains a steel core with a gap behind it that is filled with lead. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing. Used by special services of Warsaw Pact countries.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[d_red] - %c[ui_gray_2] sub-sonic ammunition\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] greatly increased projectile drop with distance</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-gauss_descr">
		<text>Batteries that use a capsulated fragment of the "Flash" artefact as their power source. Manufactured using hi-tech equipment.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]armored stalkers
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] prototype</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-gauss_cardan_descr">
		<text>These lower-capacity cells use capsulated fragments of the "Flash" artefact as their power source. Their lower capacity is due to makeshift production conditions and lack of specialised equipment.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1] armored stalkers
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] prototype</text>
	</string>

    <!-- BAS ammo -->
	<string id="ammo_23x75_shrapnel_descr">
		<text>Cartridge with buckshot charge. Application range up to 25 meters. It is used for firing from the KS-23 carbine. Due to the fact that the barrel has rifling in the KS-23 carbine, the buckshot flies over a large area, which allows you to shoot offhand, practically without aiming.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] multiple pellets</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_23x75_barrikada_descr">
		<text>A cartridge with a steel pointed bullet. It is used to forcibly stop vehicles by damaging them. Application range up to 100 meters. It is used for firing from the KS-23 carbine.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_9x21_sp10_descr">
		<text>Pistol cartridge with a bullet of increased penetration. Designed to destroy manpower protected by personal protective equipment. The nose part of the heat-strengthened steel core protrudes from the shell, due to which a high penetration effect of the bullet is achieved.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]general purpose</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_20x70_buck_descr">
		<text>Standard 20-calibre round filled with 6 mm buckshot. Highly lethal at close range. Only suitable for use with smoothbore weapons\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants
		\n \n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] multiple pellets, shorter eff. range</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_23_eco_descr">
		<text>A special cartridge designed for the needs of the scientific staff located in the Zone. Depending on the task, it is filled with different types of solutions. Requires very careful handling. How to use: very slowly put into the weapon.\n
		\n%c[ui_gray_1]SPECIAL:\n \n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Using a thin wolfram needle, it pierces the skin of the mutants to inject the solution.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo_338_federal_descr">
		<text>The .338 Federal is a rifle cartridge based on the .308 Winchester case necked up to .33 caliber. It was created by Federal Cartridge and Sako in 2006 and intended as a big game cartridge with reasonable recoil for lightweight rifles.\n 
		\n%c[ui_gray_2] - %c[ui_gray_2] Best for: %c[ui_gray_1]mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_338_federal_s">
		<text>.338 Federal</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
