<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

    <!-- Mechanic -->
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>I had hoped a former sawmill would have some machinery left, but there's nothing but rotting logs. I could use some tools to work with. If you can find basic ones, please bring to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I had hoped a former sawmill would have some machinery left, but there's nothing but rotting logs. I could use some tools to work with. If you can find basic ones, please bring to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thanks. Things are going to be much easier with these. Hey, as thanks, I'll set aside some of my stock for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_2_about">
		<text>Since you've already found one set of tools, do you happen to know where some more advanced ones are? I desperately need some.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Since you've already found one set of tools, do you happen to know where some more advanced ones are? I desperately need some.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you, thank you. As thanks, I'll give you a small discount and access to some better stuff.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dasc_tech_mlr_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you for everything. Next time I get restocked, you'll get the best selection out of everything I have. Perhaps this wretched place will turn into a fully fledged camp someday.</text>
	</string>

<!-- Dark Valley Raiders Companion Dialog -->

	<string id="bandit_companion_task_1_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Lead the way, we'll be right behind you. You'll get your cut when we're done. Just watch our backs while we're filling our pockets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_companion_task_1_start_dialog_2">
		<text>We should get moving - my trigger finger is getting itchy. Just remember, the loot is ours!</text>
	</string>
	<!--Bandit medic-->
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_text">
		<text>The bandit medic needs %s to work on medical supplies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>I'm scraping the bottom of the barrel, trying to find enough bandages and medkits for everyone who gets injured every day. We're about to find out what happens when we don't have any meds left, if I can't get one of those old drug-making kits. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I've been looking all over for a %s. It's got the stuff I need to make my own meds and supplies. I'll pay you well for one of those kits, if you can get me a full set.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Toolkits for Limpid -->
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>Limpid needs %s to install basic equipment upgrades.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Perfect! This is just what I need, man. I can properly upgrade gear now! I'll make sure you get access to the good stuff next time you're back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>Limpid needs %s to install advanced equipment upgrades.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>You followed through again! Good deal man. One friend to another, I'll make sure you get dibs on my next restock.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>Limpid needs %s to install expert equipment upgrades.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_3_bandit_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>You followed through again! Good deal, man, here's some cash for your trouble. And I'll make sure you're the best-equipped member of the crew, just come by after my next shipment.</text>
	</string>

	<!--Bandit radiant quests-->
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>There are a few guys who need someone to take them out shopping, if you catch my drift. Scout out some prime targets for them, and you'll get a nice cut when the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>This one's a cinch. Sultan's got a mind to shake down a nearby stalker camp, shake things up, remind them who's in charge around here. You'll need to get your own little gang together for this, but there's a big prize in it for you if you can pull it off.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Ha! Well done! I hope you stripped them bare and got your fill of their loot. Here's a little extra from me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_5_finish">
		<text>So they tried to pay you with bullets, huh? Typical free loaders. As for you, here's your prize.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>